buzzjack.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy Policy - BuzzJack Music Forum

BuzzJack Enthusiast

Group: Members  
Posts: 877  
Member No.: 3,326 

Joined: 1-May 07

BuzzJack Entertainment Forums ("BuzzJack") Privacy Policy

Introduction  
Buzzjack respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site solely in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies exclusively to information collected at Buzzjack's Web site. By visiting Buzzjack, you're accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

When you visit the Buzzjack website, the server automatically collects a limited amount of information from your computer essential for the site's operation and security. We collect this information through the use of automatically generated server logs.

Information collected includes your computer's IP address, the name of your Internet Service Provider, information concerning your browser and operating system, as well as the page visited prior to accessing our website. This information is used to perform statistical analysis of user trends and interests and to help us make this site more useful to visitors. Buzzjack does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

In browsing the major portions of our site, users do not need to provide any personally identifiable information about themselves. However, in order to proceed through certain segments of our website, Buzzjack collects personally identifiable information, such as when contacting Buzzjack etc. In these cases information collected could include you name.

Buzzjack does make limited use of cookies on some portions of our site, but not in any manner that could intrude upon your privacy. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive as a unique identifier. Our cookies do have an expiration date. Buzzjack uses cookies in this case to simplify and enhance the browsing experience. 

Buzzjack provides links to / or content from other Web sites. When you click on links to other Web sites or view content from other Web Sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours, and we can take no responsibility for information collected on other sites linked to from our site. 

The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources. We do not share data with third parties.

Buzzjack is dedicated to preventing unauthorized data access, maintaining data accuracy, and ensuring the appropriate use of information. We strive to put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial safeguards in order to secure the information we collect online. To this end we use regular backups.

If problems arise, users may contact Buzzjack. We are committed to resolving disputes in a timely manner.

Buzzjack reserves the right to remove any information deemed inappropriate or an infraction of these terms of use at its sole discretion. Buzzjack also reserves the right to terminate anyone's access to our services without notice, at any time, for any reason.

Please be advised that our privacy policy may change over time. Users are encouraged to check it regularly for updates or alterations.
